Guide to the BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
- Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Code no.8511: Association of Contracting Plumbers of the City of New York and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada, Local 2, 1960-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8512: Plumbing Contractors Association of Chicago and Cook County and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada, Local 130, 1959-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8515: Association of Master Painters and Decorators of the City of New York and Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, District Council No. 9, 1959-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8516: Peninsula Area Painters and Decorators Joint Committee and District Council of Painters, Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, Local 33, 1959-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    1959-1962 1965-1968
  - Code no.8517: Builders' Association of Kansas City and Painters District Council No. 3 of the Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, 1960-1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8519: Chicago Council of the Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Painters' District Council No. 14 of the Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, 1960-1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8520: Painting and Decorating Employers' Association and Painters' District Council No. 35 of the Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, 1963-1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8522: Western Washington Chapters of the Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Western Washington Painters, Locals 924, 339, 5, 801, 64, 743, Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Code no.8524: Greater Detroit and Wayne Chapters of the Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Painters' District Council 22 of the Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, 1960-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8525: Pittsburgh Chapter, Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Painters Local Union No. 6, Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, 1961-1967 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8528: Southeastern Michigan Chapter, National Electrical Contractors Association of Detroit and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 58, 1961-1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8530: Philadelphia Division of the Penn-Del-Jersey Chapter of the N.E.C.A. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 98, 1958-1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8531: Southeast Texas Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, local 716, 1961-1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8534: Nassau and Suffolk Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 25, 1961-1967 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8535: Orange County Chapter, National Electrical Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 441, 1960-1969 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8536: Puget Sound Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors' Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46, 1962-1969 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8537: New York Electrical Contractors' Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3, 1958- 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8541: South Florida Chapter of the Associated General Contractors of America and Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterer's Union of America, Local 7, 1966-1972 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8557: Master Plasterers' Association of Boston and Vicinity and Easter Massachusetts Laborers' District Council, 1959-1969 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Code no.8569: General Building Contractors Association, Inc. and Metropolitan District Council of Philadelphia and Vicinity, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1964-1975 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Code no.8592: Northeastern States Boilermaker Employees and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1970-1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Code no.8593: Connecticut Construction Industries Association and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 478, 1974- 1977 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Code no.8597: Associated General Contractors of America, Alaska Chapter and Building and Construction Trades Department, AFL-CIO, 1961- 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Code no.8600: Electrical Contractors' Association of City of Chicago and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 134, 1970- 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Code no.8605: Labor Relations Division of the Ohio Contractors Association, Associated General Contractors of America and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 18, 18A, 18B, 1961-1965 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8608: Construction Employers Association and Falls Cities Carpenters District Council and Affiliated Unions, Louisville, Kentucky, 1962- 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8615: Negotiating Committee of the Niagara Frontier Builders Association and Carpenters District Council of Buffalo, New York and Vicinity, 1961-1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8628: Master Carpenters' Association, Cement League, Hollow Metal Door and Buck Association and District Council of New York City and Vicinity, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1960-1966 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8629: Oklahoma Chapter, Builders' Division, Associated General Contractors of America and Carpenters Local 329, Oklahoma City, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1962-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8631: Oregon-Columbia Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America and Oregon State Council, Portland and Vicinity District Council, 1962-1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8636: Dayton Area Construction Industry Association and Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers, Local 1410, 1960- 1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8637: Associated Building Contractors of Colorado, Inc. and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 720, 1961- 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8642: Associated General Contractors of America, Oklahoma Chapter, Builders Division and International Hod Carriers, Construction and General Laborers Union of America, AFL, Local 612, 1961-1969 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Code no.8647: Utah State Lathing and Plastering Contractors Association and Laborers District Council of Utah, Locals 79, 206, 653, 1960- 1964 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8650: Associated Building Contractors, Toledo Home Plastering Contractors Association, Inc. and International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers Union, Local 500, 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8664: Associated General Contractors of New Jersey and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 825, 825A, 825B, 825C, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8667: Associated Underground Contractors and International Hod Carriers' Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 1191, 1076, 1962-1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8668: Labor Relations Division of Michigan Road Builders Association and International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers, Local 1191, 1961-1970 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8671: General Contractors Association of Bridgeport, CT and Construction and General Laborers' Union, Local 665, 1963- 1975 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8677: Metro Detroit Plumbing and Mechanical Contractors and United Association of Plumbing and Pipefitting, Local 636, 1974- 1977 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8678: Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts, Inc.; Building Trades Employers' Association of Boston and Eastern Mass. and Bricklayers and Masons, Local 3 of Boston, AFL- CIO, 1963-1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8679: Pennsylvania Heavy and Highway Contractors Bargaining Association and International Union of District 50 United Workers of America, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8680: Madison Employers Council and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 464, 1967-1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8681: Independent Building Metal Companies and International Association of Iron Workers, Local 580, 1963-1966 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Code no.8682: Contractors Association of Westchester County and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 137, 137A, 137B, 137C, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Code no.8686: Associated Plumbing and Air Conditioning Contractors of Nevada and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry, Local 525, 1963-1966 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Code no.8688: Associated Building Contractors of Colorado, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council of Denver and Vicinity, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Code no.8690: Minnesota Chapter, National Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 110, 1963- 1974 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Code no.8693: Associated General Contractors of America, Detroit Chapter and Cement Masons' Union, Local 514, Detroit, AFL, 1964- 1976 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Code no.8697: Eastern New York Construction Employers and International Hod Carriers' Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, Locals 190, 157, 452, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Code no.8698: Associated General Contractors, Knoxville, Tennessee Chapter and Knoxville Building and Construction Trades Council, 1968- 1973 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Code no.8699: Mason Contractors Association of Baltimore, Maryland and Bricklayers' and Masons P&B Union No.1, 1967- 1975 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Code no.8700: Heavy Construction and Excavating Contract and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 282, 1963-1969 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Code no.8701: Associated Building Contractors of Colorado, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 9, 1963- 1975 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Code no.8702: Mechanical Contractors, District of Columbia Association, Inc. and United Association of Plumbing and Pipefitting, Local 5, 1963-1966 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Code no.8714: Associated General Contractors of New Jersey and International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforced Ironworkers, Locals 11, 45, 373, 480, 483, 1965-1977 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Code no.8717: General Building Contractors Association, Inc. and Laborers' District Council of the Metropolitan Area of Philadelphia and Vicinity, 1963-1970 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Code no.8718: General and Sub-Contractors' Associations and Laborers' District Council of Eastern Pennsylvania, affiliated with International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Code no.8724: Illinois Road Building and Excavating Companies and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 150, 1966- 1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8730: Idaho Branch, Inc. of the Associated General Contractors of America and State of Idaho District Council of Laborers, affiliated with the Laborers International Union of North America, AFL- CIO, 1966-1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8733: Builders Association of South Florida, Inc. and Laborers International Union of North America, Local 478, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8745: Oregon-Columbia Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America and Joint Council of Teamsters, No. 37, affiliated with the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1964-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8751: General Contractors of Jacksonville and Vicinity and Carpenters District Council of Jacksonville and Vicinity, 1966- 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8752: Contractors of Albuquerque, New Mexico and Laborers International Union of North America, Local 16, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8754: Associated Brick Mason Contractors of Greater New York and General Building Laborers' Local 66, 1972-1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8756: Building Trades Employers Association of Long Island, Inc. and General Building Laborers' Local 66, 1966-1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8757: Long Island Building Contractors Association; Building Trades Employers Association, Suffolk and Nassau Counties and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council of Nassau and Vicinity, AFL, 1961-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Code no.8760: Building Employers' Association of Broward County, Florida and Construction and General Laborers' Union 938 of Laborers' International Union, AFL-CIO, 1966-1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8761: Idaho Branch, Inc. of the Associated General Contractors of America and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 370, 1966-1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8763: South Florida Chapter of the Associated General Contractors of America and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 349, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8764: Industrial Contractors and Builders Association of Indiana and International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforced Ironworkers, Local 395, 1966-1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8765: Labor Relations Division of the Ohio Contractors Association, Associated General Contractors of America and Lake Erie District Council of Carpenters, 1966-1971 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8766: Broward Boulders Exchange, Inc. and Broward County Carpenters' District Council of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1966-1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8775: Sheboygan Division, Electrical Contractors Association, Milwaukee Chapter and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 494, 1966-1971 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8776: Westchester-Fairfield Chapter, National Electrical Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 501, 1965-1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8779: Chattanooga Chapter, Associated General Contractors and Tri-State Carpenters and Joiners, District Council of Chattanooga, Tennessee and Vicinity, 1967-1976 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8780: Building Trades Employers' Association and Cleveland Area International Union of Operating Engineers, District 1, 1967- 1970 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Code no.8781: Electrical Contractors Association of Greater Boston, Inc.; Boston Chapter, National Electrical Contractors Association and Electrical Workers Union, Local 103, 1966-1972 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Code no.8785: Southern Illinois Builders Association and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 520, 1966-1970 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Code no.8791: Cleveland Plumbing Contractors' Association and Cleveland Journeyman Plumbers, Local 55 of the United Association, 1967- 1973 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Code no.8799: Great Lakes Fabricators and Erectors Association and International Association of Bridge, Structural, and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 25, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Code no.8802: Houston Sheet Metal Contractors Association and Sheet Metal Workers' Local Union, Local 54, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Code no.8807: Associated Brick Mason Contractors of Greater New York and Mason Tenders' District Council of Greater New York, 1966- 1975 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Code no.8808: Operating Engineers Employers of Eastern Pennsylvania and Delaware and International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO, Local 542, 542A, 542B, 1965-1973 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Code no.8809: Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO, Local 542, 542A, 542B, 1969-1975 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Code no.8810: Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and Metropolitan District Council of Philadelphia and Vicinity, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1965-1973 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Code no.8830: Associated Contractors of Ohio, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 18, 18A, 18B, 18RA, 1970- 1975 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Code no.8832: Building Trades Employers Association of Columbus, Ohio and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 18, 18A, 18B, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Code no.8833: Plumbing, Heating, and Piping Employers, Council of Northern California and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry, Local 393, 1966-1975 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Code no.8834: Colorado Contractors Association, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 13, 1969-1975 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Code no.8835: Home Builders and District Contractors Association of Palm Beach County, Inc.; Florida East Coast Chapter of Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Palm Beach County Carpenters District Council, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Code no.8850: Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts, Inc.; Building Trades Employers' Association of Boston and Eastern Mass. and Newton Carpenters' District Council, AFL-CIO, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Code no.8856: Central Ohio Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, AFL-CIO, Local 200, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Code no.8891: Independent Employers and Mason Tenders' District Council of Greater New York, 1972-1981 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Code no.8893: Building Trades Employers' Association of Western Massachusetts and Carpenters District Council of Holyoke and Vicinity; Pioneer Valley District Council; Springfield Local Union 32, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Code no.8896: New Mexico Building Branch Associated General Contractors of America and New Mexico Building and Construction Trades Council, AFL-CIO; New Mexico District Council of Carpenters, AFL-CIO, 1963-1978 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Code no.8900: Association of Concrete Contractors of Long Island, Inc. and General Building Laborers' Local 66, 1972-1981 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Code no.8905: Oklahoma Chapter, Builders' Division, Associated General Contractors of America and International Hod Carriers Building and Common Laborers Union of America, Local 1202, 1961-1971 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Code no.8921: Associated General Contractors of Florida, East Coast Chapter and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 675, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Code no.8928: Florida West Coast Chapter, National Electrical Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 915, 1964-1974 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Code no.8930: National Electrical Contractors Association, Alaska Chapter and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1547, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Code no.8934: Associated General Contractors of America, San Diego Chapter and San Diego District Council of Carpenters, 1974- 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8845 / 551841: Associated General Contractors of Illinois and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1965- 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8587 / 591068: Field Construction Employers in Ohio, Kentucky and West Virginia and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Locals 40, 105, 139, 667, 1961-1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8867 / 591253: Oregon-Columbia Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America and International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforced Iron Workers, Local 29, 1968-1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8459 / 591362: Quad-City Builders Association, Inc. and Tri-City Carpenters District Council, 1964-1977 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8653 / 591619: Iron League of Chicago, Inc. and Architectural and Ornamental Iron Workers Union, Local 63, 1963-1968 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
  - Code no.208: Hygrade Food Products Corporation and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1970- 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Code no.208: Hygrade Food Products Corporation, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Code no.208: Hygrade Food Products Corporation, Livonia, Michigan and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Code no.248: AGRIPAC, Inc. and Teamster Food Processors, Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local Union 670, Salem Oregon, 1973- 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Code no.248: Blue Lake Packers, Inc. (division of AGRIPAC, Inc.) and Cannery Warehousemen, Food Processors, Drivers and Helpers, Local 670, Salem, Oregon, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Code no.280: N/A and Cake Bakers Union, Local 51, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Code no.307-1: Brewers Board of Trade and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local Unions 1, 3, 8, 46, 124, 323, 1059, 1096, 1345, 1956-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Code no.358-1: NYC Bakery Employers Labor Council and Local Union 50, American Bakery and Confectionery Workers Union, 1962- 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Code no.394-1: Del Monte Corporation and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 760, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Code no.394-1: California Packing Corporation and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 760 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Code no.395: Star-Kist Foods and United Cannery and Industrial Workers of the Pacific, Los Angeles and Vicinity District; affiliated with Seafarers International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Code no.398: Adolph Coors Company, Golden, Colorado and Brewery, Bottling, Can and Allied Industrial Union, Local 366, AFL-CIO, 1974- 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Code no.622-2: Plain Dye and Machine Print Companies and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    1963-1966, 1969-1974
  - Code no.814-2: California Sportswear and Dress Association and Los Angeles Dress and Sportswear Joint Board (of the Ladies International Garment Workers' Union), 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Code no.814-3: California Sportswear and Dress Association and Los Angeles Dress and Sportswear Joint Board (of the Ladies International Garment Workers' Union), 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Code no.819-2: Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers' Association and Los Angeles Joint Board of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Code no.819-3: Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers' Association and Los Angeles Joint Board of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Code no.832: New Jersey Apparel Contractors Association and International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, Local Union 10, 1967- 1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Code no.847: Children's Dress Association and International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, Local 91, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Code no.871: Association of Rain Apparel Contractors, Inc. and Waterproof Garment Workers' Union, Local 20 and Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Code no.1624-1: American Viscose Corporation, Fibers Division and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Code no.1624-2: FMC Corporation, American Viscose Division, Fiber Operations and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1942- 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2102: Associated Shoe Industries of Southeastern Massachusetts and Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)